k12jobspot.com 2010-11-21

# Privacy - K12JobSpot.com

K12JobSpot is committed to maintaining the privacy of all users. The following policies describe how the website collects, manages, and uses the information submitted by users. Use of this website indicates that a user has read these policies and agrees to abide by them. 

K12JobSpot (“this website”) collects information that may make users personally identifiable on a voluntary basis only. 

Upon registration, the user’s name and email are required. Other information such as street address, telephone number, professional certifications, educational degrees, and other information will be optional and may be included at a user's discretion. Users will also have the option to release their candidacy profile to potential employers, including but not limited to school districts, that have agreements with the website and partner company, General ASP Inc. 

General ASP Inc. will not share personally identifiable information with third parties for the purposes of marketing or solicitation. General ASP Inc. may use personal information, including but not limited to telephone number, email address, and mailing for marketing its own products to registered users of the website. Users will have the ability to choose to receive email-based communication from the website at time of registration. General ASP Inc. may collect non-personally identifiable information in aggregate from user profiles for the purpose of statistical compilation and analysis only. Any user information collected for statistical purposes or disclosed to third parties for any reason will be on an anonymous basis only. 

User information such as IP address, internet service provider, web browser, operating system, approximate times of use, referring site, or any similar data exchanged between a user's computer and the servers of K12JobSpot is collected on an aggregate basis and is not used to personally identify a particular user account. 

The website uses “cookies,” or small set of data messages, to track what users view while on the website. These cookies do not record personally identifiable information and are only used to allow convenient access to content on behalf of the user. For example, cookies allow a user to return to and edit a job posting or resume. 

Only direct employees and programmers within the website staff will have access to user information. This access includes, but is not limited to, modification or deletion of information as needed to maintain the integrity of the user database and to improve the website’s performance and connectivity. 

The information collected and stored by K12JobSpot will be stored on servers within the United States. Use of the website outside of the United States and its territories and holdings assumes consent to the transfer of information into the United States. 

The website maintains appropriate technical and management measures to keep user information secure and safe from damage, corruption, loss, or deletion. However, the website cannot guarantee absolute protection from third parties with malicious intentions. Users must recognize that their own web browsers are part of the security process. When submitting personal information, users should ensure that a closed lock, key, or other symbol is visible to indicate that a page is secure.   
Users can choose to delete their account completely at anytime. If a user wishes to do so, the user should contact a K12JobSpot service representative. Methods of contact appear at the end of this policy. 

Should the security measures or information handling practices of this website ever change, the modifications will be posted in the Privacy Policy. Users who are concerned about how their information is used should contact a K12JobSpot service representative at General ASP Inc. 

K12JobSpot service representatives at General ASP Inc. welcome all questions and concerns via email, telephone, or fax.
